{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559027417","data":{"timestamp":" 947559027416"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559027794","data":{"timestamp":" 947559027794"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559028281","data":{"timestamp":" 947559028281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559028634","data":{"timestamp":" 947559028634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559029045","data":{"timestamp":" 947559029045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559029529","data":{"timestamp":" 947559029528"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559029760","data":{"timestamp":" 947559029759"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559033035","data":{"timestamp":" 947559033035"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559033069","data":{"timestamp":" 947559033069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559033782","data":{"timestamp":" 947559033782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559034175","data":{"timestamp":" 947559034175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559034468","data":{"timestamp":" 947559034468"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559034671","data":{"timestamp":" 947559034671"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559034863","data":{"timestamp":" 947559034863"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559035177","data":{"timestamp":" 947559035177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559035400","data":{"timestamp":" 947559035400"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559038654","data":{"timestamp":" 947559038654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559039063","data":{"timestamp":" 947559039063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559041594","data":{"timestamp":" 947559041594"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559041801","data":{"timestamp":" 947559041801"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559042009","data":{"timestamp":" 947559042009"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559045557","data":{"timestamp":" 947559045557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559049325","data":{"timestamp":" 947559049322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559050368","data":{"timestamp":" 947559050368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559053094","data":{"timestamp":" 947559053093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559053472","data":{"timestamp":" 947559053472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559053959","data":{"timestamp":" 947559053959"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559054310","data":{"timestamp":" 947559054310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559054722","data":{"timestamp":" 947559054722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559055205","data":{"timestamp":" 947559055205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559055438","data":{"timestamp":" 947559055437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559058719","data":{"timestamp":" 947559058717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559058770","data":{"timestamp":" 947559058770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559059501","data":{"timestamp":" 947559059501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559059901","data":{"timestamp":" 947559059901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559060201","data":{"timestamp":" 947559060201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559060417","data":{"timestamp":" 947559060417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559060622","data":{"timestamp":" 947559060621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559060953","data":{"timestamp":" 947559060952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559061184","data":{"timestamp":" 947559061184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559063819","data":{"timestamp":" 947559063817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559063914","data":{"timestamp":" 947559063913"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 15590a25-8b8b-4b2f-bd0a-94244409c021"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559077164","data":{"timestamp":" 947559077163"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559077998","data":{"timestamp":" 947559077998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559078713","data":{"timestamp":" 947559078712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559078927","data":{"timestamp":" 947559078927"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559079481","data":{"timestamp":" 947559079481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559080285","data":{"timestamp":" 947559080285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559080659","data":{"timestamp":" 947559080659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559081323","data":{"timestamp":" 947559081322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559084017","data":{"timestamp":" 947559084017"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559084216","data":{"timestamp":" 947559084216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559084880","data":{"timestamp":" 947559084879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559085546","data":{"timestamp":" 947559085546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559086214","data":{"timestamp":" 947559086214"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559086846","data":{"timestamp":" 947559086844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKA"," userResponse":" KICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559087067","data":{"timestamp":" 947559087067"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559087965","data":{"timestamp":" 947559087965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAHARI"," userResponse":" KALAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559091217","data":{"timestamp":" 947559091216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559091847","data":{"timestamp":" 947559091847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559092642","data":{"timestamp":" 947559092642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559093276","data":{"timestamp":" 947559093276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559094316","data":{"timestamp":" 947559094314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559094833","data":{"timestamp":" 947559094833"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559095700","data":{"timestamp":" 947559095700"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559096485","data":{"timestamp":" 947559096485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559097238","data":{"timestamp":" 947559097238"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559098014","data":{"timestamp":" 947559098013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559100405","data":{"timestamp":" 947559100404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559101292","data":{"timestamp":" 947559101289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559102165","data":{"timestamp":" 947559102164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559102535","data":{"timestamp":" 947559102534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559103021","data":{"timestamp":" 947559103020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559103743","data":{"timestamp":" 947559103742"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559104182","data":{"timestamp":" 947559104182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559104956","data":{"timestamp":" 947559104955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZINI"," userResponse":" ZIZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559107321","data":{"timestamp":" 947559107317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559108083","data":{"timestamp":" 947559108082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559108648","data":{"timestamp":" 947559108648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559109164","data":{"timestamp":" 947559109164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559109679","data":{"timestamp":" 947559109678"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559112184","data":{"timestamp":" 947559112183"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" NENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559113300","data":{"timestamp":" 947559113300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMTAFUTE"," userResponse":" UKAMTAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559113624","data":{"timestamp":" 947559113624"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559116640","data":{"timestamp":" 947559116640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEZEEKA"," userResponse":" NIMEZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559117208","data":{"timestamp":" 947559117207"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559117855","data":{"timestamp":" 947559117855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559118782","data":{"timestamp":" 947559118782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUKIMU"," userResponse":" KUKUKIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559119228","data":{"timestamp":" 947559119228"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559120403","data":{"timestamp":" 947559120403"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559120870","data":{"timestamp":" 947559120870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559121721","data":{"timestamp":" 947559121721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559123689","data":{"timestamp":" 947559123688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559124405","data":{"timestamp":" 947559124404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559125057","data":{"timestamp":" 947559125057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559125876","data":{"timestamp":" 947559125875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559126477","data":{"timestamp":" 947559126476"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559126665","data":{"timestamp":" 947559126665"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559127604","data":{"timestamp":" 947559127604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559128050","data":{"timestamp":" 947559128049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559128937","data":{"timestamp":" 947559128936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559132429","data":{"timestamp":" 947559132429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559133310","data":{"timestamp":" 947559133310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559133798","data":{"timestamp":" 947559133798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559135063","data":{"timestamp":" 947559135063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOANGAZA"," userResponse":" KILICHOANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559135620","data":{"timestamp":" 947559135620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559135769","data":{"timestamp":" 947559135768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559136314","data":{"timestamp":" 947559136314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559139019","data":{"timestamp":" 947559139019"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559140156","data":{"timestamp":" 947559140156"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559140695","data":{"timestamp":" 947559140694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559143502","data":{"timestamp":" 947559143502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559144757","data":{"timestamp":" 947559144757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559145519","data":{"timestamp":" 947559145519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559146194","data":{"timestamp":" 947559146194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559147039","data":{"timestamp":" 947559147038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559147891","data":{"timestamp":" 947559147891"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559150325","data":{"timestamp":" 947559150325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559150809","data":{"timestamp":" 947559150808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559151329","data":{"timestamp":" 947559151329"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559151840","data":{"timestamp":" 947559151840"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559152484","data":{"timestamp":" 947559152484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559155963","data":{"timestamp":" 947559155963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559155989","data":{"timestamp":" 947559155988"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559156463","data":{"timestamp":" 947559156463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559157227","data":{"timestamp":" 947559157227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559158190","data":{"timestamp":" 947559158190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559158833","data":{"timestamp":" 947559158833"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559158839","data":{"timestamp":" 947559158839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559161593","data":{"timestamp":" 947559161592"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559161923","data":{"timestamp":" 947559161922"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559162102","data":{"timestamp":" 947559162101"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559162999","data":{"timestamp":" 947559162998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559165367","data":{"timestamp":" 947559165366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBONA"," userResponse":" MBONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559165620","data":{"timestamp":" 947559165619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKO"," userResponse":" UKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559166484","data":{"timestamp":" 947559166484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559166982","data":{"timestamp":" 947559166981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559169299","data":{"timestamp":" 947559169298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559169528","data":{"timestamp":" 947559169528"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559169967","data":{"timestamp":" 947559169967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559170649","data":{"timestamp":" 947559170648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559170663","data":{"timestamp":" 947559170663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559171492","data":{"timestamp":" 947559171491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559173970","data":{"timestamp":" 947559173970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559174600","data":{"timestamp":" 947559174600"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559175828","data":{"timestamp":" 947559175828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINIACHA"," userResponse":" WALINIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559176379","data":{"timestamp":" 947559176379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559177243","data":{"timestamp":" 947559177241"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559178054","data":{"timestamp":" 947559178054"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHAMA"," userResponse":" WALIHAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559180999","data":{"timestamp":" 947559180999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUTAKA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559181968","data":{"timestamp":" 947559181967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIBEBA"," userResponse":" KUNIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559182882","data":{"timestamp":" 947559182881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559183311","data":{"timestamp":" 947559183310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559183493","data":{"timestamp":" 947559183493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559183933","data":{"timestamp":" 947559183933"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559184446","data":{"timestamp":" 947559184446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559187354","data":{"timestamp":" 947559187354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559188207","data":{"timestamp":" 947559188203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559189009","data":{"timestamp":" 947559189009"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559189414","data":{"timestamp":" 947559189414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559190295","data":{"timestamp":" 947559190294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559190317","data":{"timestamp":" 947559190317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559191111","data":{"timestamp":" 947559191111"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559193389","data":{"timestamp":" 947559193389"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559194447","data":{"timestamp":" 947559194446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUBEBA"," userResponse":" NITAKUBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559197604","data":{"timestamp":" 947559197603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPELEKA"," userResponse":" NITAKUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559198510","data":{"timestamp":" 947559198509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559199491","data":{"timestamp":" 947559199491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUJULISHE"," userResponse":" NIKUJULISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559199802","data":{"timestamp":" 947559199802"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559200569","data":{"timestamp":" 947559200569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559203145","data":{"timestamp":" 947559203144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559203987","data":{"timestamp":" 947559203986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559204779","data":{"timestamp":" 947559204779"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIBEBA"," userResponse":" NIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559207629","data":{"timestamp":" 947559207629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559208876","data":{"timestamp":" 947559208875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USILALAMIKE"," userResponse":" USILALAMIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559209386","data":{"timestamp":" 947559209386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559209700","data":{"timestamp":" 947559209700"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559210392","data":{"timestamp":" 947559210392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559211254","data":{"timestamp":" 947559211254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAVYOWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559212188","data":{"timestamp":" 947559212187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHIMILI"," userResponse":" KUHIMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559212861","data":{"timestamp":" 947559212861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559213762","data":{"timestamp":" 947559213761"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559216354","data":{"timestamp":" 947559216352"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559217045","data":{"timestamp":" 947559217044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559217760","data":{"timestamp":" 947559217759"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559218375","data":{"timestamp":" 947559218374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559219049","data":{"timestamp":" 947559219048"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559219429","data":{"timestamp":" 947559219429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559220070","data":{"timestamp":" 947559220069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559220658","data":{"timestamp":" 947559220658"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559221247","data":{"timestamp":" 947559221247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559222194","data":{"timestamp":" 947559222194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559222861","data":{"timestamp":" 947559222861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559223323","data":{"timestamp":" 947559223322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559224021","data":{"timestamp":" 947559224021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559224454","data":{"timestamp":" 947559224454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559227177","data":{"timestamp":" 947559227177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559228016","data":{"timestamp":" 947559228016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559228579","data":{"timestamp":" 947559228579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559228778","data":{"timestamp":" 947559228777"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559229260","data":{"timestamp":" 947559229260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559229784","data":{"timestamp":" 947559229784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559230488","data":{"timestamp":" 947559230488"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559231068","data":{"timestamp":" 947559231068"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559231845","data":{"timestamp":" 947559231844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559233860","data":{"timestamp":" 947559233859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559234557","data":{"timestamp":" 947559234556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559235287","data":{"timestamp":" 947559235286"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559235666","data":{"timestamp":" 947559235666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559236357","data":{"timestamp":" 947559236356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559239048","data":{"timestamp":" 947559239047"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559239731","data":{"timestamp":" 947559239731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559240454","data":{"timestamp":" 947559240453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559241081","data":{"timestamp":" 947559241080"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559241767","data":{"timestamp":" 947559241766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559242150","data":{"timestamp":" 947559242149"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559242781","data":{"timestamp":" 947559242781"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559243367","data":{"timestamp":" 947559243367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559243963","data":{"timestamp":" 947559243963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559244922","data":{"timestamp":" 947559244921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559245586","data":{"timestamp":" 947559245585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559246051","data":{"timestamp":" 947559246051"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559246763","data":{"timestamp":" 947559246762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559247193","data":{"timestamp":" 947559247193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559249870","data":{"timestamp":" 947559249870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559250704","data":{"timestamp":" 947559250704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559251263","data":{"timestamp":" 947559251263"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559251463","data":{"timestamp":" 947559251463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559251947","data":{"timestamp":" 947559251947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559252477","data":{"timestamp":" 947559252477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559253178","data":{"timestamp":" 947559253178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559253766","data":{"timestamp":" 947559253766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559254538","data":{"timestamp":" 947559254538"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559257062","data":{"timestamp":" 947559257062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559257762","data":{"timestamp":" 947559257762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559258491","data":{"timestamp":" 947559258491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559258868","data":{"timestamp":" 947559258867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559259566","data":{"timestamp":" 947559259565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559263035","data":{"timestamp":" 947559263034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559263652","data":{"timestamp":" 947559263651"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559264195","data":{"timestamp":" 947559264195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPYA"," userResponse":" MAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559264894","data":{"timestamp":" 947559264893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559265317","data":{"timestamp":" 947559265317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559266072","data":{"timestamp":" 947559266071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559266265","data":{"timestamp":" 947559266264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559266626","data":{"timestamp":" 947559266626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559267235","data":{"timestamp":" 947559267235"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGINE"," userResponse":" MENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559268053","data":{"timestamp":" 947559268053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559270303","data":{"timestamp":" 947559270303"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559270870","data":{"timestamp":" 947559270869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559271672","data":{"timestamp":" 947559271671"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559272768","data":{"timestamp":" 947559272767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," userResponse":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559273321","data":{"timestamp":" 947559273320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559274022","data":{"timestamp":" 947559274022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559274609","data":{"timestamp":" 947559274609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559275669","data":{"timestamp":" 947559275669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559276383","data":{"timestamp":" 947559276382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559276876","data":{"timestamp":" 947559276876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559841799","data":{"timestamp":" 947559841798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559841882","data":{"timestamp":" 947559841881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559852306","data":{"timestamp":" 947559852306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559860167","data":{"timestamp":" 947559860165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559865811","data":{"timestamp":" 947559865810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559992211","data":{"timestamp":" 947559992206"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 783534fb-5ec1-4765-9445-fa62bc44cc36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559992304","data":{"timestamp":" 947559992304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 42e30c52-376c-438a-876b-f27d94c9e296"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUTHONI"," userResponse":" MUTHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947559998682","data":{"timestamp":" 947559998682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 42e30c52-376c-438a-876b-f27d94c9e296"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947560004903","data":{"timestamp":" 947560004903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 42e30c52-376c-438a-876b-f27d94c9e296"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947560010361","data":{"timestamp":" 947560010361"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" 42e30c52-376c-438a-876b-f27d94c9e296"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_61"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa nimekuwa msichana mkubwa lakini ninamkosa rafiki yangu Muthoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947560050640","data":{"timestamp":" 947560050640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_055013"," gameId":" ff23ce4c-4f1e-4afb-a90e-c2f8460e7df5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}